[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "We have to as a nation examine our souls and say, how did we come to this?", "question_tokens": ["We", "have", "to", "as", "a", "nation", "examine", "our", "souls", "and", "say", ",", "how", "did", "we", "come", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "It was really, I found, horrifying, because I watched the whole thing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "really", ",", "I", "found", ",", "horrifying", ",", "because", "I", "watched", "the", "whole", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "If you can't get angry over the cold-blooded murder of 20 school children age 6 and 7 years old, when the hell do you get angry?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "ca", "n't", "get", "angry", "over", "the", "cold-blooded", "murder", "of", "20", "school", "children", "age", "6", "and", "7", "years", "old", ",", "when", "the", "hell", "do", "you", "get", "angry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "That's problem.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What would you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "-- when your heard the address by Wayne LaPierre?", "question_tokens": ["--", "when", "your", "heard", "the", "address", "by", "Wayne", "LaPierre", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Yes, I think the NRA missed a huge opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "the", "NRA", "missed", "a", "huge", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wayne LaPierre"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Are you a member of the NRA yourself or?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "member", "of", "the", "NRA", "yourself", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "What is your view about the specific campaign which I have been pursuing and the president is pursuing and others are pursuing which is not about banning guns, it's about banning assault weapons, getting the kind of weapons which can massacre school classrooms, these military-style machines, getting those off the streets?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "the", "specific", "campaign", "which", "I", "have", "been", "pursuing", "and", "the", "president", "is", "pursuing", "and", "others", "are", "pursuing", "which", "is", "not", "about", "banning", "guns", ",", "it", "'s", "about", "banning", "assault", "weapons", ",", "getting", "the", "kind", "of", "weapons", "which", "can", "massacre", "school", "classrooms", ",", "these", "military-style", "machines", ",", "getting", "those", "off", "the", "streets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "DT", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Right, when you have such a tragedy like we did, it was such a dark day for this nation.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "when", "you", "have", "such", "a", "tragedy", "like", "we", "did", ",", "it", "was", "such", "a", "dark", "day", "for", "this", "nation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "You think assault weapons should be banned or not?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "assault", "weapons", "should", "be", "banned", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "That's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sandy Hook School"], "LOCATION": ["Oregon", "Aurora"]}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Please?", "question_tokens": ["Please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "The particular assault weapon that massacred the children at the Sandy Hook School, was the same one used at the Oregon shopping mall mass shooting and in Aurora in the movie theater.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "particular", "assault", "weapon", "that", "massacred", "the", "children", "at", "the", "Sandy", "Hook", "School", ",", "was", "the", "same", "one", "used", "at", "the", "Oregon", "shopping", "mall", "mass", "shooting", "and", "in", "Aurora", "in", "the", "movie", "theater", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "What I never hear back from anyone who defends them is what other purpose can they possibly have than mass slaughter?", "question_tokens": ["What", "I", "never", "hear", "back", "from", "anyone", "who", "defends", "them", "is", "what", "other", "purpose", "can", "they", "possibly", "have", "than", "mass", "slaughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "RBS", "RB", "VBZ", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "What is your view about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I don't see how video games can contribute to violence in that manner, especially when most video games is emulate real life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "how", "video", "games", "can", "contribute", "to", "violence", "in", "that", "manner", ",", "especially", "when", "most", "video", "games", "is", "emulate", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "What is the answer?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "First of all, this is not as rare as people might think.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "this", "is", "not", "as", "rare", "as", "people", "might", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What is going to change this culture?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "to", "change", "this", "culture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Piers, this is what's going to change it.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "this", "is", "what", "'s", "going", "to", "change", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "But as she said, people should be trained for these use, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "she", "said", ",", "people", "should", "be", "trained", "for", "these", "use", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What law do you propose that would have stopped this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "law", "do", "you", "propose", "that", "would", "have", "stopped", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Here's what I think: you have to try.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "what", "I", "think", ":", "you", "have", "to", "try", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Why don't you tell me, Mr. Lott?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "tell", "me", ",", "Mr.", "Lott", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Lott"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 492, "question": "How many bullets can it fire in a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "can", "it", "fire", "in", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "There's a reason --", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "reason", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 502, "question": "How many bullets does the AR 15 fire a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "does", "the", "AR", "15", "fire", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "The point --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "point", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Do you want to answer or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "answer", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I'm going to answer your first question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "answer", "your", "first", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How many bullets does it fire a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "does", "it", "fire", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "The point is --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "point", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Can you answer the question or not?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "answer", "the", "question", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "You will lose lives.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "will", "lose", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I think your estimate is high.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "your", "estimate", "is", "high", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "If you were trying to debate this in a more rational way than I appear capable of, what would you do?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "trying", "to", "debate", "this", "in", "a", "more", "rational", "way", "than", "I", "appear", "capable", "of", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "But I understand your passion, having stood on too many street corners, seen too many bodies, seen the kind of weapons we're pulling of the streets.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "understand", "your", "passion", ",", "having", "stood", "on", "too", "many", "street", "corners", ",", "seen", "too", "many", "bodies", ",", "seen", "the", "kind", "of", "weapons", "we", "'re", "pulling", "of", "the", "streets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What do you think of this debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "this", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "There are three points that I think need to be raised.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "three", "points", "that", "I", "think", "need", "to", "be", "raised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Do you want to see these assault rifles just gone?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "see", "these", "assault", "rifles", "just", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "You know, I think getting rid of the assault weapons, you know, it is not a perfect bill, but we will never be able to legislate against evil.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "getting", "rid", "of", "the", "assault", "weapons", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "is", "not", "a", "perfect", "bill", ",", "but", "we", "will", "never", "be", "able", "to", "legislate", "against", "evil", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121221pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I absolutely believe in banning those weapons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "believe", "in", "banning", "those", "weapons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]